attorneyforfreedom.com 2012-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Marc J. Victor

## Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 

To process transactions  

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.attorneyforfreedom.com  
3920 South Alma School Rd., Suite 5  
Chandler, AZ 85248  
USA  
jonathan@attorneyforfreedom.com  
(480) 455-5233
